Turkus, Burton B. Arbitration Files 5712
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Burton B. Turkus Arbitration Files
1926-1982
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Turkus, Burton B.
5712
26.5 cubic feet
26.5 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
The collection is arranged alphabetically by company name, except for Box No. 12 and portions of Box No. 13, which contain arbitration cases involving the International Organization of Masters, Mates and Pilots. Except as noted, all case files contain an Award. Most files, however, include much more documentation as is noted throughout the description.
3338467
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, May 16, 2000
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 28, 2019
Scope and Contents
The collection is arranged alphabetically by company name, except for Box No. 12 and portions of Box No. 13, which contain arbitration cases involving the International Organization of Masters, Mates and Pilots.
Except as noted, all case files contain an Award. Most files, however, include much more documentation as is noted throughout the description.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5525: Local 1199 Additional Files 6004: NAA Additional Records
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States.; Turkus, Burton B.
3338467
- Abilene Gallant, Inc. vs. IBT Local 553, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  1/22/77. Issue: settled
- ACME Fast Freight, Inc. vs. BRAC, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  3/4/76. Issue: Seniority - transfer. Includes: Correspondence, master Agreement, seniority roster, supporting documentation, Arbitrator's notes
- Aer Lingus Irish Airlines vs. IAMAW, District 100, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  6/6/77. Issue: Temporary employees. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, employer position paper, Agreement.
- Aer Lingus Irish Airlines vs. IAMAW, Lodge 100, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  4/10/80. Issue: settled
- Aiello Dairy Farms, Inc. vs. Retail Clerks International Association, Local 888, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  1/26/70. Issue: Rates of pay, fringe benefits - pension plans, welfare funds
- Air Canada vs. IAM, District 100, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  3/8/76. Issue: Absences - discipline. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation
- Air Canada vs. IAM, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  5/22/72. (See File Folder 14.) Issue: Discipline - suspensions.
- Air France vs. IAM, District 100, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  12/18/78. Issue: Discipline - procedural due process. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation
- Air Panama International vs. IAM District 100, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  6/14/80. Issue: Falsification of company records in general. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation, copy of Agreement, Arbitrator's notes
- Airborne Freight Corporation vs. IBT, Local 295, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  11/12/75. Issue: Alcoholism, drinking and intoxication - drinking off company premises on work time.
- Airborne Freight Corporation vs. IBT, Local 295, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  3/3/77. Issue: Contracting out bargaining unit work. Includes: supporting documentation, Agreement, Arbitrator's notes, correspondence
- Airborne Freight Corporation vs. IBT, Local 295, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  2/18/76. Issue: Overtime refusal. Includes: Supporting documentation, Arbitrator's notes, Company brief.
- Airborne Freight Corporation vs. IBT, Local 295, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  1/23/76. Issue: Contracting out bargaining unit work. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation, Arbitrator's notes.
- Air Canada vs. IAM, District Lodge 100, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  3/1/77. Issue: Discipline - tardiness, substandard work. Includes: Exhibits, supporting documentation, Arbitrator's notes, Company brief, correspondence
- Airway Equipment Rental Company, Inc. vs. IAM, Lodge 1834, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  11/15/74. Issue: Dishonesty - cheating.
- Airway Services, Inc. vs. UAW, Local 365, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  4/9/80. Issue: Demotion - discipline. Includes: Agreement, supporting documentation, correspondence.
- Albany Times Union vs. The Independent Committee, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  5/12/59. Issue: Discipline - discharge.
- Alexanders, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 840, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  10/13/82. Issue: Discipline - tardiness, substandard performance, insubordination. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation.
- Alitalia vs. IAM, District 100, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  2/1/79. Issue: Theft of customer property. Includes: supporting documentation, correspondence, Arbitrator's notes.
- Alitalia vs. IAM, District 100, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  4/15/76. Issue: Transfers - employee's right to transfer. Includes: Correspondence, Arbitrator's notes, supporting documentation.
- Alitalia vs. IAM, District 100, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  4/11/77. Issue: Fringe benefits - bonuses. Includes: Agreement, correspondence, supporting documentation.
- Alitalia vs. IAM, District 100, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  6/18/80. Issue: Absences - excessive. Includes: Supporting documentation
- Allied Aviation Service Company of New Jersey vs. BRAC, Allied Service Division, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  11/20/73. Issue: Discipline - discharge
- Allied Aviation Service International Company vs. Transport Workers of America, Local 504, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  3/26/73. Issue: Fights and altercations - assault on supervisor.
- Allied Aviation Service Company vs. IAM, District 100, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  8/4/78. Issue: Discipline - suspension. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation, Arbitrator's notes.
- Allied Aviation Service International Company vs. Transport Workers of America, Local 504, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  11/7/78. Issue: Classification of jobs - change in work assignment. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, supporting documentation.
- Allied Aviation Service Company vs. IAM, District 100, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  7/23/81. Issue: Improper personal conduct - discharge. Includes: Post-hearing memo, reply brief, Arbitrator's notes, supporting documentation
- Allied Maintenance Corporation vs. BRAC, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  1/12/76. Issue: withdrawn
- Allied Maintenance Corporation vs. Building Service Employees International, Local 307, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  8/17/70. Issue: Rates of pay - differential in pay.
- Allied Maintenance Corporation vs. Transport Workers of America, Local 504, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  6/2/78. Issue: Insurance - disability benefit. Includes: Agreement, correspondence, insurance coverage
- Allied Maintenance Corporation vs. Transport Workers of America, Air Transport Local 504, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  5/7/79. Issue: Discipline - court ruling, effect. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, supporting documentation
- Aluminum Company of America vs. OPEIU, Local 180, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  9/22/71. Issue: Insurance - disability benefits.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers of America, Air Transport Division, Local 552, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  8/10/76. Issue: withdrawn
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers of America, Air Transport Division, Local 552, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  5/12/76. Issue: Dishonesty - defrauding. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  6/2/70. Issue: Improper personal conduct - discharge.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers of America, Airline Stewards and Stewardesses Association, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  7/1/71. Issue: Improper personal conduct - theft.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers, Airline Stewards and Stewardesses Association, Local 550, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  12/7/73. Issue: Improper personal conduct - detrimental conduct.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers, Local 552, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  5/15/75. Issue: Improper personal conduct - intoxication.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers of America, Local 552, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  10/12/76. (See File Folder 14.) Issue: Improper personal conduct - discharge. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation, Arbitrator's notes
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers of America, Air Transport Division, Local 552, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  11/17/75. Issue: Discipline - discharge
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers, Local 552, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  4/21/75. Issue: Discipline - discharge.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers, Local 552, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  5/13/76. Issue: Improper personal conduct - intoxication. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers, Local 552, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  7/12/73. Issue: Improper personal conduct - sleeping on job.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers, Local 552, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  7/24/74. Issue: Improper personal conduct - intoxication.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers, Local 553, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  4/21/75. Issue: Improper personal conduct - theft.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers, Local 554, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  10/12/76. (See File Folder 11.) Issue: Improper personal conduct.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers, Local 555, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  1/31/77. Issue: Discipline - discharge (weight limits). Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation.
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers, Air Transport Division, Local 552, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  12/6/76. Issue: Discipline - discharge. Includes: Correspondence
- American Airlines vs. Transport Workers, Local 552, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  5/15/75. Issue: Improper personal conduct - intoxication. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation, Arbitrator's notes.
- American Bank Note Company vs. International Paper and Glass Cutter Union, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  4/30/79. Issue: Discipline - violation of plant rules. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation, Agreement and Master Contract
- American Bank Note Company vs. IAMAW, District 15, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  9/21/81. Issue: Fights and altercations - assault on supervisor. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation, Company brief, Arbitrator's notes.
- American Bank Stationery Company vs. Long Island Typographical Union, Local 915, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  1/26/77. Issue: Improper personal conduct - insubordination. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation
- American Broadcasting Company vs. Writers Guild of America East, Inc, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  5/17/76. Issue: withdrawn
- American Dredging Company vs. International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 25, Maine Division, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  10/4/77. Issue: withdrawn
- American Dredging Company vs. International Union of Operating Engineers, Local 25, Maine Division, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  5/8/79. Issue: withdrawn
- American Export Lines, Inc. vs. OPEIU, Local 153, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  5/20/77. Issue: Discipline - substandard performance. Includes: Supporting documentation, Company memorandum, Union brief, correspondence, Arbitrator's notes.
- American Medical Affiliates (Heritage House Convalarium) vs. Joint Board, Nursing Home and Hospital Employees, Florida Division, Local 115, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  9/24/79. Issue: Negotiations - arbitration procedure. Includes: Correspondence, Agreement, supporting documentation
- American Museum of Natural History vs. AFSCME, District Council 37, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  3/8/82. Issue: Improper personal conduct - inter-employee relations. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, supporting documentation, correspondence, Employer and Union memoranda, detailed analytical reports on handwriting?
- American Museum of Natural History vs. AFSCME, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  11/26/79. Issue: Absences - unauthorized. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation.
- American Pacific Container Lines, Inc. vs. National Maritime Union of America, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  6/12/80. Issue: Welfare funds - Employer's contribution. Includes: Supporting documentation, correspondence
- American Steakhouse Company, Inc. vs. Hotel, Restaurant, and Club Employees and Bartenders Union, Local 6, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  9/17/81. Issue: Improper personal conduct - moral turpitude. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, Agreement, correspondence, supporting documentation
- American Telephone and Telegraph Company vs. CWA, Local 2550, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  9/17/77. Issue: Improper personal conduct - discharge. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation
- Incorp National Services, Inc. vs. Hotel, Motel, Restaurant and High-rise Employees and Bartenders Union, Local 355, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  6/10/75. Issue: Improper personal conduct - standards of conduct.
- Angelo Tomasso, Inc. vs. Connecticut Labor Relations Division of New England Road Builders Association, Local 559, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  8/9/71. Issue: Improper personal conduct - standards of conduct.
- ARA Services, Inc. vs. Chefs, Cooks, Cafeteria Food, Beverage and Service Employees Union, Local 32, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  6/5/75. Issue: Discipline - leaving plant without permission; improper personal conduct - intoxication. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation, Agreement, Arbitrator's notes.
- ARA Services, Inc. vs. HREBIU, Transportation Terminal, Interplant and Commissary Food Employees Union, Local 21, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  1/7/72. Issue: Improper personal conduct - theft.
- ARA Services, Inc. vs. HRCEBU, Local 6, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  11/1/82. Issue: settled
- ARA Services, Inc. vs. HRCEBU, Local 6, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  3/12/82. Issue: Improper personal conduct - theft. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation, 1980 Agreement.
- ARA Services, Inc. vs. HRCEBU, Local 6, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  3/15/82. Issue: Improper personal conduct - theft. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, supporting documentation, correspondence, 1980 Agreement
- ARC Rebuilders, Inc. vs. International Production Service and Sales Employees Union, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  7/22/77. Issue: Union representatives and business - elections. Includes: Correspondence
- Ari-Lincoln Square Corporation vs. IBT, Local 272, Garage Employees Union, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  7/31/80. Issue: ? Includes: Supporting documentation, Arbitrator's notes, Agreement
- Arlen Realty Management Corporation vs. Hotel, Restaurant, Employees and Bartenders International Union, Local 335, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  12/14/79. Issue: Vacation pay - computation. Includes: Agreement, correspondence, supporting documentation.
- Armand Garage Corporation vs. IBT, Garage Employees Local Union 272, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  5/3/77. Issue: Improper job attitude - loafing. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation
- Arrow Group Industries, Inc. vs. USA, Local 8151, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  5/25/77. Issue: Improper personal conduct - negligence. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation, Company memorandum.
- Art Steel Company, Inc. vs. Distributive Workers of America, District 65, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  5/3/78. Issue: Layoff - lack of work. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, supporting documentation, correspondence, Agreement
- Art Steel Company, Inc. vs. UAW, District 65, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  9/30/80. Issue: Layoff - emergency. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, supporting documentation, correspondence, Agreement.
- Art Steel Company, Inc. vs. Sheet Metal Workers International Association, Local 400, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  3/2/71. Issue: Welfare funds - Employer's contribution.
- Art Steel Company, Inc. vs. Distributive Workers of America, District 65, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  6/4/79. Issue: Absences - discipline. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, Agreement, correspondence, supporting documentation.
- Associated Diamond Cab, Inc., Miami, Florida, vs. BRAC, Allied Service Division, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  2/8/73. Issue: Reinstatement
- Associated Press vs. American Newspaper Guild, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  6/17/58. Issue: Improper job attitude - general attitude.
- Associated Press vs. American Newspaper Guild, Wire Service Guild, Local 222, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  1/23/61. Issue: Overtime - rates of pay
- Associated Universities, Inc., Brookhaven National Laboratory vs. IBEW, Local 2230, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  10/21/80. Issue: settled
- Association of Catholic Schools vs. Federation of Catholic Teachers, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  12/1/78. Issue: Termination of employment - lack of work. Includes: Agreement, correspondence, supporting documentation
- Atlantic Marine Agencies, Inc. vs. NMU Pensions and Welfare Plan, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  4/23/81. Issue: settled
- Atlantic Marine Agencies, Inc. vs. NMU, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  8/17/81. Issue: Welfare fund - Employer's contribution. Includes: Correspondence
- Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Great (A&P) vs. IBT, Local 202, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  8/17/79. Issue: Discipline - substandard performance. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation, Company statement
- Aurora Products Corporation and Louis Max and Company, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 815, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  2/21/78. Issue: settled
- Automatic Connector, Inc. vs. IAMAW, District 15, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  10/3/78. Issue: Classification of jobs - error in classification. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, Agreement, correspondence, supporting documentation
- Autotote, Ltd. vs. IBEW, Local 3, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  12/14/81. Issue: settled
- AVCO Corporation vs. Michael Holodnak (Box 3, Folder 31)
  Not dated. Issue: ? Includes: Materials relating to Circuit Court decision in above case; no Award
- AVCO Corporation vs. UAW, Local 1010, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  2/13/70. Issue: Overtime - discrimination. Includes: Appeal to United States District Court
- AVCO Corporation vs. UAW, Local 1010, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  3/20/73. Issue: Improper personal conduct - concealed weapons, assaults
- AVCO Corporation vs. UAW, Local 1011, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  2/20/73. Issue: Improper personal conduct - theft.
- Barcelona Hotel vs. Hotel, Motel, Restaurant, and High-Rise Employees and Bartenders Union, Local 335, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  1/14/75. Issue: Improper personal conduct - theft. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation
- Barnard College vs. Distributive Workers of America, District 65, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  7/6/78. Issue: Termination of employment - sick leave (for psychological illness). Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation.
- Barnard College vs. Distributive Workers of America, District 65, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  7/6/78. Includes: Materials pertaining to File Folder 35.
- Beech-Nut Life Savers, Inc. vs. Candy and Confectionery Workers, Local 452, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  11/14/68. Issue: Schedule of work - management rights
- Beefsteak Charlie's vs. Hotel and Restaurant Employees and Bartenders Union, Local 69, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  12/7/77. Issue: settled
- Beefsteak Charlie's vs. HREBU, Local 6, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  9/2/80. Issue: Discipline - suspension. Includes: Correspondence.
- Beefsteak Charlie's vs. HREBU, Local 6, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  9/2/80. Issue: settled
- Beefsteak Charlie's vs. HREBU, Local 6, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  3/26/82. Issue: Improper personal conduct - standards of conduct (use of drugs). Includes: Correspondence.
- Beefsteak Charlie's vs. HREBU, Local 6, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  5/20/80. Issue: withdrawn
- Beefsteak Charlie's vs. HREBU, Local 69, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  1/21/77. Issue: Improper personal conduct - disruptive influence. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence.
- Beefsteak Charlie's vs. HREBU, Local 6, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  1/12/81. Issue: withdrawn
- Beefsteak Charlie's vs. HREBU, Local 69, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  9/4/79. Issue: Improper personal conduct - theft. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation.
- Beefsteak Charlie's vs. HREBU, Local 6, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  8/20/80 Issue: withdrawn.
- Beefsteak Charlie's vs. HREBU, Local 6, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  9/2/80. Issue: withdrawn
- Belmont Smelting and Refining Works vs. USA, District 4, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  10/16/78. Issue: withdrawn.
- Belmont Smelting and Refining Works vs. USA, District 4, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  1/3/76. Issue: Absences - discipline. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation.
- Bernstein Institute of Beth Israel Medical Center vs. SEIU, Local 144, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  2/21/78. Issue: Rates of pay - adjustment. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, supporting documentation
- Bieler National Industries, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 239, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  6/4/77. Issue: Shutdown - management rights. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation.
- Bieler National Industries, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 239, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  12/7/77. Issue: Shutdown - early quit. Includes: Agreement, Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation.
- B&K Investments, Inc. vs. Joint Board, Nursing Home and Hospital Employees, Local 1115, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  6/16/78. Issue: Contract modification - offer and acceptance. Includes: Correspondence, supporting documentation, decision of United States District Court with application to above case.
- Blackstone Retirement Residence vs. Nursing Home and Hospital Employees Division, Local 1115, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  1/10/77. Issue: withdrawn
- Booth American Shipping Corporation vs. OPEIU, Local 153, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  4/11/69. Issue: Tardiness - discipline.
- Boston Edison Company vs. Utility Workers Union of America, Local 369, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  10/19/77. Issue: Discipline - discharge. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence, supporting documentation
- Boston Edison Company vs. UWUA, Local 369, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  12/10/76. Issue: settled
- Boston Edison Company vs. UWUA, Local 369, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  11/13/79. Issue: settled
- Boston Edison Company vs. UWUA, Local 369, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 21a)
  12/22/75. Issue: Assignment of job.
- Boston Edison Company vs. UWUA, Local 387, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  10/27/80. Issue: Discipline - suspension. Includes: Agreement, correspondence, supporting documentation.
- Boston Edison Company vs. UWUA, Local 369, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  9/14/76. Issue: Improper job attitude - insubordination. Includes: Agreement, correspondence, supporting documentation.
- Boston Edison Company vs. UWUA, Local 369, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  12/22/75. Issue: Management rights - assignment of job.
- Boston Edison Company vs. UWUA, Local 369, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  3/3/77. Issue: Improper personal conduct - moral turpitude. Includes: Correspondence, Company and Union briefs.
- Boston University vs. BRAC, Allied Services Division, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  10/17/80. Issue: Improper personal conduct - sleeping on job. Includes: Agreement, correspondence, Arbitration transcript.
- Brasserie, Inc. vs. HRCEBU, Local 6, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  7/10/80. Issue: withdrawn
- Breakstone Sugar Creek Foods vs. IBT, Local 277, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  11/10/71. Issue: Improper personal conduct - dishonesty.
- Bridge Chrysler Plymouth, Inc. vs. IBT, Local 917, 1926 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  11/4/26. Issue: Discipline - discharge. Includes: Arbitrator's notes, correspondence
- British Airways vs. IAM, District Lodge 100, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  5/11/78. Issue: Assignment of jobs - temporary arrangement. Includes: Agreement, correspondence.
- British Airways vs. IAM, District Lodge 100, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 30)